Ew!
It's got someone's hair on it!
(Howard:)Oh, yeah, you're gonna
do great with this movie.
(Penny:)You're not working late.
Why did you lie to me?
(Sheldon:)And Amy, you told me you were sick,
(Sheldon:)but you look just as pale
and tired as always.
(Amy:)I'm sorry.
I just needed a break
(Amy:)from hearing you obsess about
what to do after string theory.
And we kind of just wanted one night
where we didn't have to hear
(Bernadette:)about how miserable you are
making this movie.
(Amy:)But none of that means
we don't love you.
(Penny:)I haven't been complaining
that much about the movie.
(Penny:)Have I?
(Leonard:)I also love you.
(Leonard:)You know what?
Maybe I need a break from all cf you.
(Penny:)-Come on, Sheldon.
-Where are we going?
(Penny:)We're gonna have
Anything Can Happen Thursday.
(Penny:)You're gonna tell me all about your
science stuff and I'm gonna complain
(Penny:)about my movie,
and we're gonna support each other
(Penny:)-because that's what friends do.
-Okay.